projectfastcash.com 2011-02-03

# Project Fast Cash Privicy Policy

Thank you for visiting ProjectFastCash.com's web site ("Site") located at the URL www.ProjectFastCash.com. This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout ProjectFastCash.com governing ProjectFastCash.com's use of personally identifiable information provided to ProjectFastCash.com via this Site.

## Privacy Policy Updates 

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, ProjectFastCash.com may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, ProjectFastCash.com will post its updated PrivacyPolicy on our Site located at www.ProjectFastCash.com so you are always aware of what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we may use this information. ProjectFastCash.com encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy. 

## Information Collection and Use 

You can generally visit our Site without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. However, in certain sections of this Site, to use certain services, we may require you to register for an account, or we may invite you to submit questions or comments or request information, participate in surveys, questionnaires or contests, subscribe to newsletters or participate in community forums. Due to the nature of some of these activities, we may ask that you complete and submit an online form with personally identifiable information such as your name, username, email address, contact information and credit card information.

We may use your personally identifiable information to deliver certain services, products or information you have requested, verify your authority to enter certain password protected areas of the Site, send you notices for products and/or services that you have used or that may be of interest to you, and improve the content and general administration of the Site.

If you are a registered user and post to any of the Site's community forums, other registered users of this Site may view your username and may send you emails, but they will not be able to see your actual email address. We may use your personally identifiable information to send you advertisements and other promotional information regarding our products and services or the products and services of our third party marketing partners and other communications related to the Site. 

## Children's Privacy 

ProjectFastCash.com recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. No personally identifiable information is collected by ProjectFastCash.com and ProjectFastCash.com's services and Site are not intended for children under the age of 13. ProjectFastCash.com does not target its services or this Site to children under 13. ProjectFastCash.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

## Cookies 

We may use small text files called cookies to improve overall Site experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you. Cookies must be enabled for you to use certain areas of the Site.

Advertisements that appear on this Site are delivered to users by our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may download cookies to your computer. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement. In this way, they may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. This information allows an advertising network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. ProjectFastCash.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers.

Aggregate Information The Site may track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, IP addresses, External Web Sites (defined below) linked to, and we may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may share this aggregate information with third parties to assist them in targeting advertisements to appropriate audiences. 

## Disclosure 

We may provide your personally identifiable information that we collect and the data generated by cookies to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us. For example, we may provide your personally identifiable information to an organization in order to complete a service (e.g., process your payment). 

We will also disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority. 

## Links to Third Party Sites 

The Site may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which ProjectFastCash.com does not have control ("External Web Sites"). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by ProjectFastCash.com of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that ProjectFastCash.com is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that ProjectFastCash.com is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites. 

## Security 

We may employ procedural and technological measures, consistent with industry practice. Such measures are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. ProjectFastCash.com may use encryption, secure socket layer, firewalls, internal restrictions, password protection and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information. 

## What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

## Correction/Updating Personally Identifiable Information 

ProjectFastCash.com provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us. If you wish to review or correct any information you have provided to us. 

* You may access your account and review, correct and delete your personally identifiable information

* Or you may contact us by email at: support@ProjectFastCash.com. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us or via email at: support@ProjectFastCash.com. 

## Return Policy

Currently we hold a 30 day guaranteed return policy for the ProjectFastCash.com Product. Doesn't matter the reason, simply email and we'll provide a quick refund. To claim the 200% Guarantee you must first complete and act on all of the Project Fast Cash tutorials, and still make no money. You will be asked to show proof of completion, then the 200% refund will be issued if all these criteria are met.
